<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NAP Central</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NAP Central</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NAP Country Platform October 2020</title>
      <link>/blog/2021/04/15/2021-04-15-nap-country-platform-oct2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021/04/15/2021-04-15-nap-country-platform-oct2020/</guid>
      <description>NAP Country Platform presentation of country National Adaptation Plans
 Time: 17:00 - 18:30
Organized as part of the NAP Expos, the NAP Country Platform provides a space for developing countries to present their National Adaptation Plan (NAP) to highlight their adaptation priorities and how they will design implementation. They also share the main lessons learned from their work, how they may promote collaboration with other countries, and how they would monitor progress and effectiveness of their adaptation efforts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAP Champions Webinar: Advancing adaptation through NAPs</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/10/14/2020-10-14-nap-champions-oct2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/10/14/2020-10-14-nap-champions-oct2020/</guid>
      <description>NAP Champions Webinar: Advancing adaptation through National Adaptation Plans
 Time: 14:00 - 15:30
The event discussed the importance of having a plan to guide concrete action on adaptation and subsequent monitoring and evaluation; and shared specific experience with advanced data systems in supporting systematic observation and monitoring in the important area of food systems. An interactive discussion focused on how to achieve effective plans in a timely manner by relying on best available data and making use of frontier technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advancing NAPs and climate-resilient recovery under COVID-19</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/06/09/2020-06-09-naps-june-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/06/09/2020-06-09-naps-june-2021/</guid>
      <description>Advancing NAPs and climate-resilient recovery under COVID-19 Time: 14:00 - 15:30
 The COVID-19 pandemic introduces yet another challenge to societies and systems. And like many risks of a similar kind, the impacts are greater on the already vulnerable members of society, further widening their vulnerability to other risks (existing and new). As governments embark on recovery efforts to the devastating impacts of COVID-19, it is important that such efforts build upon and contribute to resilience-building to climate change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Do you have any questions about NAPs, or you would like to get involved in NAPs in any of the developing countries? Are you interested in the Open NAP initiative and can contribute towards the formulation or implementation of a NAP for a given country? Do you have recent research results that you feel would be useful towards a NAP for any of the countries?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing Country NAPs</title>
      <link>/naps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/naps/</guid>
      <description>The following NAPs have been submitted by developing countries, and are presented here in their original languages. In cases where multiple documents were submitted to cover different langauge, as well as a summary, these are listed as separate documents to facilitate easier downloading.
    Country Name Date Submitted Title Language     Brazil 2016 Brazil NAP - English English   Brazil 2016 Brazil NAP - Portuguese Portuguese   Burkina Faso 2015 Burkina Faso NAP English   Burkina Faso 2015 Burkina Faso NAP French   Cameroon 2015 Cameroon NAP - Fench French   Chile 2017 Chile NAP - Spanish Spanish   Colombia 2018 Colombia NAP - Spanish Spanish   Ethiopia 2019 Ethiopia NAP English   Fiji 2018 Fiji NAP English   Grenada 2019 Grenada NAP English   Guatemala 2019 Guatemala NAP - Spanish Spanish   Kenya 2017 Kenya NAP English   Kiribati 2020 Kiribati NAP English   Kuwait 2021 Kuwait National Adaptation Plan 2019-2030 English   Paraguay 2020 Paraguay NAP Spanish   Saint Lucia 2018 Saint Lucia NAP English   Saint Vincent and the Grenadines 2019 Saint Vincent and the Grenadines NAP English   Sri Lanka 2016 Sri Lanka NAP English   State of Palestine 2016 State of Palestine NAP English   Sudan 2016 Sudan NAP English   Suriname 2020 Suriname NAP English   Timor-Leste 2021 TIMOR-LESTE’S NATIONAL ADAPTATION PLAN: Addressing climate risks and building c… English   Togo 2018 Togo NAP - French French   Uruguay 2019 Uruguay Agriculture NAP - Spanish Spanish   Uruguay 2019 Uruguay Agriculture NAP Executive Summary - English English   Uruguay 2019 Uruguay Agriculture NAP Executive Summary - Spanish Spanish     SECTORAL NAPS AND OTHER OUTPUTS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>There are many avenues for technical guidance and advice on the NAPs. Below are some frequently asked questions.
 SUBMITTING A NAP  How do we submit a NAP for inclusion on NAP Central? Send the document via E-mail (in pdf or Word format) with a cover email from the National Climate Change Focal Point, to the secretariat (secretariat at unfccc.int; or to any of the offers in the NAP Unit at napcentral at unfccc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAP Monitor</title>
      <link>/monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/monitor/</guid>
      <description>knitr::opts_chunk$set(echo = TRUE)R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NAP-SDG iFrame</title>
      <link>/iframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/iframe/</guid>
      <description>knitr::opts_chunk$set(echo = TRUE)R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open NAPs</title>
      <link>/open-naps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/open-naps/</guid>
      <description>What is the Open NAP initiative? The Open NAP initiative provides support to developing countries in preparing and implementing their NAP, by crowd-sourcing relevant organizations, experts and networks to offer technical advice and assistance.
Current Open NAP projects? Comoros Lesotho Malawi Sao Tome &amp;amp; Principe </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
