<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nap-champion on NAP Central</title>
    <link>/tags/nap-champion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nap-champion on NAP Central</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/nap-champion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NAP Champions Webinar: Advancing adaptation through NAPs</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/10/14/2020-10-14-nap-champions-oct2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/10/14/2020-10-14-nap-champions-oct2020/</guid>
      <description>NAP Champions Webinar: Advancing adaptation through National Adaptation Plans
 Time: 14:00 - 15:30
The event discussed the importance of having a plan to guide concrete action on adaptation and subsequent monitoring and evaluation; and shared specific experience with advanced data systems in supporting systematic observation and monitoring in the important area of food systems. An interactive discussion focused on how to achieve effective plans in a timely manner by relying on best available data and making use of frontier technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advancing NAPs and climate-resilient recovery under COVID-19</title>
      <link>/blog/2020/06/09/2020-06-09-naps-june-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2020/06/09/2020-06-09-naps-june-2021/</guid>
      <description>Advancing NAPs and climate-resilient recovery under COVID-19 Time: 14:00 - 15:30
 The COVID-19 pandemic introduces yet another challenge to societies and systems. And like many risks of a similar kind, the impacts are greater on the already vulnerable members of society, further widening their vulnerability to other risks (existing and new). As governments embark on recovery efforts to the devastating impacts of COVID-19, it is important that such efforts build upon and contribute to resilience-building to climate change.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
